<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Oregon Trail | The Tiger Times</title><link>http://tigertimes.netlify.app/tag/oregon-trail/</link><atom:link href="http://tigertimes.netlify.app/tag/oregon-trail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Oregon Trail</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© The Tiger Times</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>http://tigertimes.netlify.app/images/icon_hua2ec155b4296a9c9791d015323e16eb5_11927_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url><title>Oregon Trail</title><link>http://tigertimes.netlify.app/tag/oregon-trail/</link></image><item><title>Oregon Trail</title><link>http://tigertimes.netlify.app/post/21-04-23-1-oregon-trail/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tigertimes.netlify.app/post/21-04-23-1-oregon-trail/</guid><description>
&lt;figure >
&lt;a data-fancybox="" href="the_oregon_trail.jpeg" >
&lt;img src="the_oregon_trail.jpeg" alt="" >
&lt;/a>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>We’re back on this adventurous journey! We just passed through Fort Laramie. Our AMAZING Wagon Train Leader convinced the guards to let the un-sick people through. All of us re-stocked on supplies. Now we’re heading through the treacherous South Pass, which is filled with rocky hills and bumps. We tied young pines to our wagons so that they would slow us down by dragging on the ground with their branches. However, one day, the Smiths were leading us when a mishap struck. Their wagon crossed over a bumpy rock and their axel broke! Then, their wagon went racing down the rocky hill, the young pines useless. Their wagon landed at the foot of the hill and broke in many pieces! The Smiths were all right and most of their supplies were too. Their animals were fine as well. But their wagon was destroyed. The wagon train decided to put some supplies on the wagons, while the rest would be loaded onto the animals, as they were fine. We would go to Fort Bridger (which was really nearby) and buy a new wagon later.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Oregon Trail</title><link>http://tigertimes.netlify.app/post/21-04-09-1-oregon_trail/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tigertimes.netlify.app/post/21-04-09-1-oregon_trail/</guid><description>
&lt;figure >
&lt;a data-fancybox="" href="http://tigertimes.netlify.app/post/21-04-09-1-oregon_trail/the_oregon_trail_hucf967c33f389130ab619766a81118218_141305_2000x2000_fit_q75_lanczos.jpeg" >
&lt;img data-src="http://tigertimes.netlify.app/post/21-04-09-1-oregon_trail/the_oregon_trail_hucf967c33f389130ab619766a81118218_141305_2000x2000_fit_q75_lanczos.jpeg" class="lazyload" alt="" width="900" height="595">
&lt;/a>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>As you know, we have been on the Oregon Trail for 46 days, and we are right now in the middle of current day Nebraska. Our journey had been uneventful but one frightful day, a thunderstorm occurs!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Lightning flashes, clouds rumble, and rain pounds down. The dirt trail turns sloshy, and one wagon turns over! The poor Websters lose all their food!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Luckily, we are only nine days away from the nearest trading point, Fort Laramie. The Websters have a decent amount of money left so they can buy more food. Until we reach Fort Laramie, each family will have to share some food with the Websters.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As if that wasn’t bad enough, 3 days away from Fort Laramie, a disease broke out on our wagon train! The Smiths, Millers, and Lucy Fletcher caught a mystery illness. The Millers died! To save the Smiths and Ms. Lucy, we used clues and found out the secret disease to get the antidote.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It was Cholera! Cholera was quite common in the 1840’s. It can be caused by contaminated food and water. Its symptoms are high fever, vomiting, thirst, and diarrhea. Its cure is rehydrated.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>