<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Issue 2 | The Tiger Times</title>
    <link>/category/issue-2/</link>
      <atom:link href="/category/issue-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Issue 2</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© The Tiger Times</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hua2ec155b4296a9c9791d015323e16eb5_11927_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Issue 2</title>
      <link>/category/issue-2/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTA Updates</title>
      <link>/post/21-04-23-6-pta-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/21-04-23-6-pta-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/home&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;img.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;walk-a-thon&#34;&gt;Walk-a-thon&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The walk a thon is a fundraiser set up by Medina PTA and it started on Wednesday and ends on Friday. Each tiger will be a walkathon shirt and on Wednesday, April 7, 2-5pm and Sat, April 24, 11am-2pm you can wear your walk a thon shirt and crazy hair-optional you can win prizes for Most miles walked – 1 per grade level (total of 6 winners). Track your miles &lt;a href=&#34;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/walkathon#logs&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.
Craziest hair/ accessories – more detail &lt;a href=&#34;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/walkathon#crazy&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.
You can also buy raffle tickets to enter into get a prize at the live events only.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/walkathon#kickoff&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Click here if you want to learn more.&lt;/a&gt;
Runners Club:
From 4-7 to 4-27 the PTA has set up a blue glitter route and orange glitter route has been set up. You can walk or run along these paths and do a little scavenger hunt. When you finish the walk, you can go to &lt;a href=&#34;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/clubs/runners#mapsand&#34;&gt;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/clubs/runners#mapsand&lt;/a&gt; submit a form for the route you did. You should get an e-mail in 48 hours but if you don’t you can contact &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:runners@medinapta.org&#34;&gt;runners@medinapta.org&lt;/a&gt; to confirm that they got your form. For every route you complete you can earn a foot token and a little chain for it. To find out more, go to &lt;a href=&#34;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/clubs/runners#maps&#34;&gt;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/clubs/runners#maps&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ms-veronicas-awards&#34;&gt;Ms. Veronica’s awards&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our beloved custodian Ms. Veronica has been working very hard and has been awarded the “Well maintained equipment award” and the “Well maintained school award”. This is even better because not only did she win those rewards she won them during a pandemic. All in all we give our thanks to Ms. Veronica for keeping our school clean and keeping our hybrid friends safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;talent-show&#34;&gt;Talent Show&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Wednesdays May 5 2021 6:30 pm you can see Medina’s got talent by going here &lt;a href=&#34;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/events/talent-show&#34;&gt;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/events/talent-show&lt;/a&gt; and scrolling down. To submit your video for the talent show go to &lt;a href=&#34;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/events/talent-show&#34;&gt;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/events/talent-show&lt;/a&gt; don’t miss it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;runners-club&#34;&gt;Runners Club:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From 4-7 to 4-27 the PTA has set up a blue glitter route and orange glitter route has been set up. You can walk or run along these paths and do a little scavenger hunt. When you finish the walk, you can go to  &lt;a href=&#34;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/clubs/runners#maps&#34;&gt;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/clubs/runners#maps&lt;/a&gt; and submit a form for the route you did. You should get an e-mail in 48 hours but if you don’t you can contact &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:runners@medinapta.org&#34;&gt;runners@medinapta.org&lt;/a&gt; to confirm that they got your form. For every route you complete you can earn a foot token and a little chain for it. To find out more, go to  &lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;https://medinapta.membershiptoolkit.com/clubs/runners#maps&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;


















&lt;figure &gt;


  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;Walk-a-ton.png&#34; &gt;


  &lt;img src=&#34;Walk-a-ton.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;  &gt;
&lt;/a&gt;



&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Suggestions</title>
      <link>/post/21-04-23-4-book-suggestions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/21-04-23-4-book-suggestions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Looking for your next read? Here are 4 suggestions from your classmates. Maybe the book you are looking for is one of them!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Candy Shop War
Rated: 4.99 stars, rated by Natalie Diefenbach&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you trap a tiger
Rated: 5 stars, rated by Danya Shah&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charlotte’s Web
Rated: 5 stars, rated by Berenice Lui&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chinese Cinderella
Rated: 4.5 stars, rated by Sahana Somanna&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Read Aloud, Stand up Yumi Chung</title>
      <link>/post/21-04-23-5-read_aloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/21-04-23-5-read_aloud/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;





  



  
  











&lt;figure &gt;


  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;/post/21-04-23-5-read_aloud/yumi_chung_hub5b321bfdf3c331149d844fb5b9a1820_104394_2000x2000_fit_q75_lanczos.jpeg&#34; &gt;


  &lt;img data-src=&#34;/post/21-04-23-5-read_aloud/yumi_chung_hub5b321bfdf3c331149d844fb5b9a1820_104394_2000x2000_fit_q75_lanczos.jpeg&#34; class=&#34;lazyload&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;596&#34; height=&#34;596&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;



&lt;/figure&gt;

Yumi’s sister Yuri has quit medical school and is not answering her phone. Meanwhile Yumi almost got revealed as Yumi to Phillipe but managed to say that Kay is her English name. At comedy camp Yumi came up with a plan to get her parents to transfer her to PAMS. Her plan is to trick her parents to come to the Haha Club to see her perform and get them to be impressed, then ace the SSAT to show that she can get great grades while having fun with comedy. She convinced her mom to let her go to the senior center but they didn’t know that she was doing comedy. She cracked some jokes but her 2nd one was not popular and it offended Sienna. When she went home her dad is so pumped up because he is installing the karaoke section.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Trail</title>
      <link>/post/21-04-23-1-oregon-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/21-04-23-1-oregon-trail/</guid>
      <description>

















&lt;figure &gt;


  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;the_oregon_trail.jpeg&#34; &gt;


  &lt;img src=&#34;the_oregon_trail.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;  &gt;
&lt;/a&gt;



&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re back on this adventurous journey! We just passed through Fort Laramie. Our AMAZING Wagon Train Leader convinced the guards to let the un-sick people through. All of us re-stocked on supplies. Now we’re heading through the treacherous South Pass, which is filled with rocky hills and bumps. We tied young pines to our wagons so that they would slow us down by dragging on the ground with their branches. However, one day, the Smiths were leading us when a mishap struck. Their wagon crossed over a bumpy rock and their axel broke! Then, their wagon went racing down the rocky hill, the young pines useless. Their wagon landed at the foot of the hill and broke in many pieces! The Smiths were all right and most of their supplies were too. Their animals were fine as well. But their wagon was destroyed. The wagon train decided to put some supplies on the wagons, while the rest would be loaded onto the animals, as they were fine. We would go to Fort Bridger (which was really nearby) and buy a new wagon later.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Debate</title>
      <link>/post/21-04-23-7-the-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/21-04-23-7-the-debate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;img.png&#34; alt=&#34;img.png&#34;&gt;
On April 20th, we had a debate based on why we should or should not worry about robots taking over human jobs. We had 2 debates on this topic. The first debate, the Yes side was Berenice, Ira, Silvia, Angela and Yabin. For the No side we had Julie, Yijia, Anushka, Victoria, and Natalie. For the second debate, the Yes side was Sahana, Audrey, Anna, Lily, and Sarah. And for the No side we had Brendon, Eugene, Eunsol, Danya, and T Sai Priyam. Both debates did an amazing job and we are patiently waiting for the results and the winners. This debate topic was an interesting one and the things we learned while researching for the debate were fascinating. Did you know that Roughly half of all the robots in the world are in Asia, 32% in Europe, and 16% in North America?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we did during Spring break</title>
      <link>/post/21-04-23-3-spring-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/21-04-23-3-spring-break/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;interview-with-student-michelle-z--mrs-behans-class&#34;&gt;Interview with student Michelle Z. , Mrs. Behan’s class.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Me]: What did you do on break?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Michelle]: I did homework and watched movies. I also read a lot of books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Me]: Did you go anywhere?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Michelle]: No, I stayed home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Me]: What was your favorite part about the break?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Michelle]: I got to wake up late.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;interview-with-student-anna-z--mrs-kaminoffs-class&#34;&gt;Interview with student Anna Z. , Mrs. Kaminoff’s class.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Me]: What did you do on this break?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Anna]: I got a bird. I went to Keechelus Lake. It was a 1hour drive. I got to play with a bunch of peeps. Then I just got to sleep in. Yeah. That’s pretty much it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;interview-with-student-sai-priyam-p--mrs-kaminoffs-class&#34;&gt;Interview with student Sai Priyam P. , Mrs. Kaminoff’s class.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Me]: What did on the break?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Sai Priyam]: I did a lot of things. 1. I went to the beach. 2. We saw some seals and crabs and starfish and fish. 3. I had a playdate with my friend. That’s all I think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Me]: Ok! Question two. What was your favorite part about this break?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Sai Priyam]: Playing in the waves at the beach.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polls</title>
      <link>/post/21-04-23-2-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/21-04-23-2-poll/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week&amp;rsquo;s poll was about:
&lt;img src=&#34;img_1.png&#34; alt=&#34;img_1.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
